soccergaming.com 2001-12-15

# Soccer Gaming - Privacy Statement

3W Pty Ltd has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this network of websites known as Soccer Gaming. 

Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

Our network uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our network. 

Our network's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and shared with other companies who may want to contact our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our network. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our network, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

This network contains links to other networks. **Soccer Gaming** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web networks. 

Our network uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers. The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our network. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our network, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our network. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our network, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

We run contests on our network in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our network. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our network, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our network. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web network, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies. 

Our web site uses ad servers (such as DoubleClick) to serve the advertisements that you see on the pages of our web site. That partner may use cookies in the process of serving advertisements, but it will not collect any personally identifiable information about you. For more information about DoubleClick, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please [click here](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy). 

### Public Forums

This network makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

### Supplementation Information

This network supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. 

### Children's Guidelines

This network collects online contact information from children without prior parental consent or parental notification. 

This network collects personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent. 

This network distributes to third parties personally identifiable information collected from children without prior parental consent. 

This network gives children the ability to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. 

At any time, a parent or legal guardian may revoke his/her consent or refuse to allow us further use of his/her child's personal information and request that we delete the information. Effecting such a request can be accomplished using the contact information provided on the relevant Network site. Please note that a site may terminate any service provided to the child if the deleted information at issue is reasonably necessary for the child's participation in that activity. 

### Choice/Opt-Out

Our network provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This network gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [unsubscribe@soccergaming.com](mailto:unsubscribe@soccergaming.com)

### Correct/Update

This network gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [update@soccergaming.com](mailto:update@soccergaming.com)

### Contacting the Web network

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this network, or your dealings with this Web network, you can contact Matt Holme 3W Pty Ltd matt@soccergaming.com
